Thaddeus Laffitte II

Greater Phoenix Area



thaddeuslaffitteii@gmail.com



4805149934



linkedin.com/in/thaddeus-laffitte-ii-643b59109

Summary

I worked in management for 4+ years. I am currently taking courses for Full Stack Development. I worked as a General Manager of a restaurant franchise, in this role I; developed and promoted multiple associates, oversaw day to day operations, worked on financials decreasing labor usage by creating a productive team.

Experience



Restaurant Manager

Fox Restaurant Concepts May 2023 - Present (6 months)



General Manager

la Madeleine French Bakery & Cafe Aug 2022 - May 2023 (10 months)



Assistant General Manager

la Madeleine French Bakery & Cafe Apr 2022 - Aug 2022 (5 months)



Restaurant Manager

la Madeleine French Bakery & Cafe Oct 2021 - Apr 2022 (7 months)



🤰 General Manager

Panda Restaurant Group

Mar 2021 - Oct 2021 (8 months)

Overseeing daily business operations. Hiring and training staff. Analyzing accounting and financial data. Generating reports and giving presentations.



Restaurant Manager

la Madeleine French Bakery & Cafe

Sep 2018 - Mar 2021 (2 years 7 months)

Leading and managing restaurant. Ordering product for the restaurant, and maintaining inventory at profitable margins as well as overseeing food quality.



Catering Specialist

la Madeleine French Bakery & Cafe

Sep 2018 - Jul 2020 (1 year 11 months)

Oversee presentation and education of client based catering. Build sale for restaurant through catering department.

Education



陷 Mountain Pointe High School

High School Diploma

Aug 2015 - 2019

During this time in High School I organized a variety of clubs and participated in honors and AP societies.

Licenses & Certifications



🕟 Notary Public Commission - SECRETARY OF STATE, ARIZONA

Issued 2020 - Expires Feb 2024 575905

ServSafe Manager - National Restaurant Association

Issued Feb 2021 - Expires Nov 2022 15760256

- CS101 Bootcamp Udemy
- Introduction to Cloud Computing Coursera QDHE9FNSJ26G
- Introduction to Web Development with HTML, CSS, and Javascript Coursera 9253RM6L2WHM
- Getting Started with Git and Github Coursera PV3BHYQPHY5U

Skills

GitHub • Git • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • Web Development • Cloud Computing • Timelines • Problem Solving • Team Leadership